<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Officer</string>
    <string name="missing_permissions">Missing Permissions</string>
    <string name="accessibility_label">Officer Accessibility</string>
    <string name="accessibility_description">To detect if a power menu is opened, Officer needs accessibility settings. You can be rest assured that this setting has no other malicious intent.</string>
    <string name="admin_label">Officer Admin Access</string>
    <string name="admin_description">Now you may think why does this app require Device Admin access, but hey, if someone tries to shutdown your phone when it is locked you would want to prevent it, right? Officer uses this privilege to lock your screen such situation comes up.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_dialog_title">Grant Accessibility</string>
    <string name="accessibility_dialog_message">On Android 13 and above, accessibility permission is blocked by default for applications that are not downloaded from the Google Play Store. However, you can still enable it by following these steps:\n\n
    1. Try to enable the accessibility by clicking on \"Grant Accessibility Permission\" button above.\n
    2. You will most probably see a \"Restricted Setting\" message. Make sure you open the popup dialog
    saying \"For your security, this setting is currently unavailable\".\n
    3. Only after this, go to App info page of this app and click on three dots menu in top right corner.\n
    4. Click \"Allow restricted settings\".\n\n\n<u>Note:</u> This is an open source application. Rest assured that this setting has no other malicious intent.</string>
    <string name="go_to_app_info">Go to app info</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="use_strict_security">Use strict security</string>
    <string name="strict_security_settings">Strict Security Settings</string>
    <string name="strict_security_desc">Turn screen off automatically for a specific time if tried to power off from lock screen. Less convenient, but more secure.</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="strict_security_info">When this setting is on, if someone opens the power menu from the lock screen, the screen will turn off automatically.
        A timer will then start, and during this time, the screen will turn off again if turned on. Once the timer ends, you can use your phone normally.
        If someone tries to open the power menu again, the timer restarts. This makes it much harder for a thief to shut down the phone before it locks.</string>
    <string name="set_timer_duration">Set timer duration in seconds</string>
    <string name="use_custom_trigger">Use custom trigger</string>
    <string name="set_custom_info">Different phone manufacturers have different event triggers which get broadcasted when the power menu is opened. Hence, there is no one-size-fits all solution. Here, you can manually trigger the power menu and the app will detect a few related events which were broadcasted. Try out all the options in the list of events below and select an option which works for your device.</string>
    <string name="set_custom_trigger_desc">Set a custom trigger point for locking the screen. If the app is not working on your device, try setting this up.</string>
    <string name="listening_for_events">Please open your device\'s power menu.\nListening for events…</string>
    <string name="setup">Setup</string>
    <string name="configure">Configure</string>
    <string name="detected_events">Detected events:</string>
    <string name="detected_events_hint">Generally, a power menu will have a name similar to \"Global Actions Dialog\".</string>
    <string name="choose_a_trigger_from_the_options_below">Choose a trigger from the options below:</string>
    <string name="current_trigger">Current trigger: </string>
    <string name="save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses">Open Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="view_source_code">View Source Code</string>
    <string name="changelog">Changelog</string>

<!--    Release Note Strings-->
    <string name="r1.0.0">- Initial release</string>
    <string name="r1.0.1">- Added custom triggers\n- Moved About section to new page\n- Added Changelog page\n- Added open source licenses
    \n- Migrated buttons to match expressive theming\n- Added new fonts: Google Rounded Sans, Bagel Fat\n- Fixed issue where title appeared behind status bar</string>
    <string name="about_app">About App</string>
</resources>